Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.9
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 9 Locals, 2.
  - Local 901
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, January 4-June 30, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 22, 1937; 16.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding John Wilding Paper, May 22, 1937; 17.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding White Collar, June 14, 1937; 18.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Mailing List and Marion Organization, June 15, 1937; 19.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Mishawaka Organization, June 15, 1937; 20.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Carey Visit, June 24, 1937; 21.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Strikes, June 30, 1937; 22.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, July 13, 1937-March 24, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 78)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, July 13, 1937; 1.
      - Owens to James Carey Regarding National Labor Relations Board, August 13, 1937; 2.
      - Owens Telegram to Carey Regarding National Labor Relations Board, August 14, 1937; 3.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 21, 1937; 4.
      - Owens to James Matles Regarding Company Union and National Labor Relations Board, September 14, 1937; 5.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Local 1236 United Mine Workers of America Strikes, September 17, 1937; 6.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Factionalism, September 23, 1937; 7.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Capehart Strikes and Finances, October 7, 1937; 8.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances and Peru, October 27, 1937; 9.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Factionalism, November 2, 1937; 10.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 12, 1937; 11.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Factionalism and District Council, December 3, 1937; 12.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, Finances and Decatur General Electric, December 6, 1937; 13.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances, December 23, 1937-March 3, 1938; 14-15.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Finances, March 4, 1938; 16.
      - Owens to Sherman Minten Regarding Refugees with April 1, 1938, Owens Letter to Carey, March 31, 1938; 17.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 24, 1938; 18.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, April 1, 1938-January 20, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding Holub Case, April 1, 1938; 1.
      - Owens to District 9 and Per Capita, April 7-15, 1938; 2-3.
      - Owens to James Matles Regarding Unemployment, April 27, 1938; 4.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Vacations, Unemployment and Grievances, April 30, 1938; 5.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding General Electric Conference, May 21, 1938; 6.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Lockouts and Philco, August 16, 1938; 7.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 903, August 22, 1938; 8.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, August 22, 1938; 9.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and 1938 UE Convention, August 29, 1938; 10.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding UE Constitution and District 9 Officers, September 26, 1938; 11.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding "Workers of the World Unite" with Pope Leo XIII Quote, September 29, 1938; 12.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Huntington Organization, September 29, 1938; 13.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding 1938 UE Convention, October 21, 1938; 14.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Maytag Defense Fund, October 21, 1938; 15.
      - Owens to James Carey Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization, December 6, 1938; 16.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Local 901 Officers, December 6, 1938; 17.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Dues and Local 1222 Mergenthaler Strikes with November 19, 1938, Alvin Hyatt Letter, December 16, 1938; 18.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Grievances, December 29, 1938; 19.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Alliance Electric, December 27, 1938; 20.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Fort Wayne Congress of Industrial Organization, Per Capita and Factionalism, January 10, 1939; 21.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Political Action and UE News, January 20, 1939; 22.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, March 6-August 31, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, March 6, 1939; 1.
      - Owens to James Carey Regarding Employment, and Brown and Brockmayer, April 26, 1939; 2.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, April 4, 1939; 3.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Local 901 Picnic, May 3, 1939; 4.
      - Owens to James Matles Regarding Wire Industry with Leaflet, June 2, 1939; 5.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Newspaper Strikes, June 2, 1939; 6.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Negotiations, June 5, 1939; 7.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Dues, June 6, 1939; 8.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Worlds Fair, June 16, 1939; 9.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Times Study Conference, June 27, 1939; 10.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Overtime, June 28, 1939; 11.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Seniority, June 29, 1939; 12.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Overtime, July 3, 1939; 13.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Finances Regarding Indianapolis, July 7, 1939; 14.
      - Owens Telegram to Matles Regarding Supplies, July 20, 1939; 15.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901 and Pattern Makers Inter-union Rivalry, August 8, 1939; 16.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding 1939 UE Convention, August 14, 1939; 17.
      - Owens Telegram to Matles Regarding Local 901, August 15, 1939; 18.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901 and Pattern Makers Inter-union Rivalry, August 16, 1939; 19.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901 and Negotiations with Organizational Summary, August 22, 1939; 20.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Standard Transformer, August 31, 1939; 21.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, September 18, 1939-January 22, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to James Matles Regarding Local 901 Organization with Proposed Letter and Second Draft Proposed Letter, September 18, 1939; 1.
      - Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding Negotiations, September 18, 1939; 2.
      - Owens to James Carey Regarding Bunting Health, September 22, 1939; 3.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901 and Postal Permit Form, September 30, 1939; 4.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Contracts, October 28, 1939; 5.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, October 30, 1939; 6.
      - Owens Telegram to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, October 31, 1939; 7.
      - Owens Telegram to Matles Regarding Vacations, November 6, 1939; 8.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry and National Labor Relations Board, November 20, 1939; 9.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Officers and Factionalism with Note, December 7, 1939; 10.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Officers and Factionalism, December 12, 1939; 11.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901 Organization and Officers, December 21, 1939; 12.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Local 902 and Factionalism, January 8, 1940; 13.
      - Owens to Local 902 Executive Board Regarding Local 902 and Factionalism, January 8, 1940; 14.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, January 10, 1939; 15.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901, Women and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, January 16, 1940; 16.
      - Owens to Viola Pascoe Regarding Local 902 and Finances, January 22, 1940; 17.
      - Owens to Andrew Schorr Regarding Local 902, January 22, 1940; 18.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Factionalism, Local 901 and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, January 22, 1940; 19.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, February 2-May 31, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to James Matles Regarding Adress Change, February 2, 1940; 1.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, February 3, 1940; 2.
      - Owens to James Carey Regarding Local 902 and Factionalism, February 6, 1940; 3.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901, International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry and Decatur General Electric with Membership List, February 15, 1940; 4.
      - Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers, March 1, 1940; 5.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Local 901, International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry and United Auto Workers with Local 901 Letter to Maintenance Machinists, March 7, 1940; 6.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901, March 8, 1940; 7.
      - Owens Telegram to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, March 9, 1940; 8.
      - Owens Telegram to UE Regarding Local 901, March 28, 1940; 9.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, April 4, 1940; 10.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Locals 901 and 924, April 25, 1940; 11.
      - Owens to Underwood Typewriter Regarding Underwood Strikes, May 8, 1940; 12.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Grievances, Wages, Factionalism and Local 901, May 8, 1940; 13.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901, International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry with Local 901 Letter to Unit A, May 31, 1940; 14.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, June 10-September 30, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 83)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to James Matles Regarding Factionalism and Grievances with Note, June 10, 1940; 1.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901, Wages, Grievances, Pensions and International Association of Machinists, June 18, 1940; 2.
      - Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding Unemployment with Lay-off List, June 24, 1940; 3.
      - Owens to James Carey Regarding Factionalism, July 9-12, 1940; 4-5.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Vacations and Illness with May 3, 1939, Vacation Plan, July 1, 1940; 6.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Seniority, July 1, 1940; 7.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Factionalism, July 31, 1940; 8.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Headquarters Dedication, August 12, 1940; 9.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, August 16, 1940; 10.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding National Labor Relations Board, September 3, 1940; 11.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Carey Visit, September 11, 1940; 12.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Detroit Wire Die Strikes with Clipping, September 17, 1940; 13.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Grievances, September 18, 1940; 14.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, September 24, 1940; 15.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Local 901, September 24, 1940; 16.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Contracts, September 28, 1940; 17.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Negotiations and Sub-contracting, September 30, 1940; 18.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, October 19, 1940-July 14, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 84)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding Negotiations, October 19, 1940; 1.
      - Owens Telegram to James Matles Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry and National Labor Relations Board, October 25, 1940; 2.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, November 8, 1940; 3.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding General Electric Conference, November 19, 1940; 4.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, November 19, 1940; 5.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Women, December 5, 1940; 6.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Conscription, December 14, 1940; 7.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Wages, February 3, 1941; 8.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Grievances, February 20, 1941; 9.
      - Owens Telegram to Matles Regarding Factionalism, March 3, 1941; 10.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Grievances, May 15, 1941; 11.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Unit A and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry with May 16, 1941, Local 901 Letter to Unit A, May 17, 1941; 12.
      - Owens to Carey Regarding Local 901 Picnic, June 4, 1941; 13.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Contracts and General Electric Conference, June 5, 1941; 14.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances, July 7, 1941; 15.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Grievances, July 10, 1941; 16.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances with August 4, 1941, Timothy Money Letter to Local 901 and May 12 1941, Treasury Department Letter to Local 901, July 14, 1941; 17.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, August 8, 1941-March 24, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 85)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 8, 1941; 1.
      - Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding Civil Liberties League, August 18, 1941; 2.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Finances, September 2, 1941; 3.
      - Owens Post Card to Matles Regarding Vacation, September 18, 1941; 4.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Grievances, December 29, 1941; 5.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Local 901 and Finances, December 29, 1941; 6.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 2, 1942; 7.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding 1942 UE Convention, January 9, 1942; 8.
      - Owens to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Military Personnel, January 14, 1942; 9.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Mine Mill Strikes, February 20, 1942; 10.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding United Construction Workers with February 6, 1942, Leaflet, March 12, 1942; 11.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 30, 1942; 12.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, June 16, 1942; 13.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Finances, July 7, 1942; 14.
      - Owens to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 19, 1942; 15.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Seniority and Women with Blanche McDonald Serivce Memo, November 20, 1942; 16.
      - Owens to Leo Jandreau Regarding Seniority and Women with November 20, 1942, Blanche McDonald Servide Building Memo, January 8, 1943; 17.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Membership Maintenance with List, January 15, 1943; 18.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, February 2, 1943; 19.
      - Owens to David Scribner Regarding German Bund, March 24, 1943; 20.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Bertha Scott Owens Correspondence, July 20, 1943-April 4, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 86)
      - Bertha Scott Owens to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, July 20, 1943; 1.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Veterans, September 10, 1943; 2.
      - Owens to Leo Jandreau Regarding Seniority and Staff Members, December 27, 1943; 3.
      - Owens to Jandreau Regarding Grievances with Grievance List, January 18, 1944; 4.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Montgomery Ward, May 8, 1944; 5.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Leave of Absence and Staff Members, June 12, 1944; 6.
      - Owens to M. E. Lord Regarding Staff Members and Leave of Absence, July 18, 1944; 7.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding United Furniture Workers Strikes, November 2, 1944; 8.
      - Owens to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, November 4, 1945; 9.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Per Captia, November 11, 1946; 10.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Political Action, January 24, 1947; 11.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 19, 1947; 12.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Resignations, March 5, 1947; 13.
      - Owens to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, April 4, 1947; 14.
    - Local 901 Incoming Sam McAfee Correspondence, April 24, 1940-July 28, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 87)
      - Joe Dermody Telegram Regarding Grievances, July 28, 1944; 1.
      - Julius Emspak Regarding Grievances, April 24, 1940; 2.
      - Emspak Telegram to Pittsfield, May 14, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 602, May 23, 1940; 4.
      - Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, February 15, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak Regarding Grievances, February 20, 1941; 6.
      - Emspak Regarding Vacations, Grievances and Wages, June 5, 1941; 7.
      - Emspak Regarding Seniority and Grievances, July 3, 1941; 8.
      - Emspak Regarding Grievances with Note, August 1, 1941; 9.
      - Emspak Regarding Patrolmen and Wages, September 19, 1941; 10.
      - Emspak Regarding Grievances, October 22-November 10, 1941; 11-12.
      - Emspak Regarding Bonding, December 5, 1941; 13.
      - Emspak Regarding Wages, February 13, 1942; 14.
      - Emspak Secretary Regarding Women, July 28, 1942; 15.
      - Emspak Regarding Bargaining Unit and Grievances, October 29, 1942; 16.
      - Emspak Regarding Women and Seniority, November 27, 1942; 17.
      - Emspak Regarding War Labor Board and Wages, February 12, 1943; 18.
      - Emspak Regarding Hours, February 26, 1943; 19.
      - Emspak Regarding White Collar Workers, May 26, 1943; 20.
      - Emspak Regarding Local 901 and Jandreau Unit, June 15, 1943; 21.
      - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Hours, October 23, 1942; 22.
      - Fitzgerald Telegram Regarding Jandreau Visit, November 2, 1943; 23.
    - Local 901 Incoming Sam McAfee Correspondence, August 20, 1940-September 6, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 88)
      - Leo Jandreau Regarding Grievances and Incentive, October 13, 1943; 1.
      - Jandreau Regarding Grievances, War Labor Board and Wages with December 4, 1943, G. H. Pfeif Letter to Jandreau, December 13, 1943; 2.
      - Jandreau Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, Grievances and Wages with December 29, 1943, G. H. Pfeif Letter to Jandreau, January 4, 1944; 3.
      - James Matles Regarding Supplies, August 20, 1940; 4.
      - Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 17, 1941; 5.
      - Matles Regarding Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, June 11, 1941; 6.
      - Matles Telegram Regarding Leaves of Absence, June 13, 1941; 7.
      - Matles Regarding Grievances Procedure, December 5, 1941; 8.
      - Matles Regarding Local 901 Decatur General Electric and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, December 9, 1941; 9.
      - Matles Regarding Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, February 17, 1942; 10.
      - Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 15, 1942; 11.
      - Matles Regarding Kokomo and Supercharge General Electric, and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, October 7, 1942; 12.
      - Matles Regarding Kokomo General Electric, October 14, 1942; 13.
      - Matles Regarding Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, October 21, 1942; 14.
      - Matles Telegram Regarding Local 901 and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, October 30, 1942; 15.
      - Matles Regarding Membership Maintenance, March 8, 1943; 16.
      - Matles Regarding Bud and Firings, March 8, 1943; 17.
      - Russ Nixon Regarding Firings and Aliens, May 15-June 11, 1942; 18-19.
      - David Scribner Regarding Membership Maintenance, May 26, 1943; 20.
      - Scribner Regarding Bargaining Unit and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, January 13, 1944; 21.
      - Joseph Turkowski Regarding Grievances, September 6, 1944; 22.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Sam McAfee Correspondence, November 19, 1940-May 13, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 89)
      - Sam McAfee Telegram to James Matles Regarding Pittsfield General Electric, May 13, 1942; 1.
      - McAfee Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, November 19, 1940; 2.
      - McAfee Telegram to Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, December 12, 1940; 3.
      - McAfee Telegram to Emspak Regarding Grievances, December 12, 1940; 4.
      - McAfee to James Carey Regarding Chamber of Commerce, January 21, 1941; 5.
      - McAfee Telegram to Carey Regarding Grievances and Factionalism, February 28, 1941; 6.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Negotiations, March 4, 1941; 7.
      - McAfee to Matles Regarding Locals 901 and 924, and Staff Members, April 3, 1941; 8.
      - McAfee to Members Regarding Unit A and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, May 2, 1941; 9.
      - McAfee Letter Regarding White Collar Workers with Form and Local 901 Letter to Office Workers, May 15, 1941; 10.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding General Electric Conference and Indiana Congress of Industrial Organization, May 24, 1941; 11.
      - McAfee to Matles Regarding Unit A and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, June 7, 1941; 12.
      - McAfee Telegram to Emspak Regarding Leave of Absence, June 12, 1941; 13.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Grievances with McAfee Note to Emspak, July 15, 1941; 14.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Hours, August 7, 1941; 15.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Patrol Men, August 12, 1941; 16.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Leaves of Absence, August 19, 1941; 17.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Sam McAfee Correspondence, September 12, 1941-March 4, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 90)
      - Sam McAfee Telegram to Julius Emspak Regarding Grievances, September 12, 1941; 1.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Patrol Men and Bargaining Unit, September 19, 1941; 2.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Leaves of Absence, October 4, 1941; 3.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, November 29, 1941; 4.
      - McAfee to M. E. Lord Regarding Grievances and Procedures, November 29, 1941; 5.
      - McAfee to James Matles Regarding Grievances and Procedure, November 29, 1941; 6.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Grievances and Wages, January 8, 1942; 7.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Labor Management Council with January 9, 1942, McAfee Letter to Lord, 8.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry and Grievances, January 29, 1942; 9.
      - McAfee to Matles Regarding Supercharger and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, February 11, 1942; 10.
      - McAfee to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Grievances and Factionalism, February 17, 1942; 11.
      - McAfee to Matles Regarding Guards and Bargaining Unit, February 28, 1942; 12.
      - McAfee to Fitzgerald Regarding Hours, March 4, 1942; 13.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Sam McAfee Correspondence, May 6-September 30, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 91)
      - Sam McAfee to Julius Emspak Regarding Fort Wayne Visit, Grievances, Raises and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, May 6, 1942; 1.
      - McAfee to Russ Nixon Regarding Aliens and Firings, May 19, 1942; 2.
      - McAfee to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Firings, June 18, 1942; 3.
      - McAfee to Julius Emspak Regarding Kokomo General Electric, Guards and Supercharger, June 22, 1942; 4.
      - McAfee to Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 9, 1942; 5.
      - McAfee to Emspak Regarding Women, July 24, 1942; 6.
      - McAfee to Matles Regarding District 9 Womens Conference, August 20, 1942; 7.
      - McAfee to Matles Regarding Kokomo General Electric, August 29, 1942; 8.
      - McAfee to Fitzgerald Regarding Women, September 23, 1942; 9.
      - McAfee to Fitzgerald Regarding Women and Factionalism, September 24, 1942; 10.
      - McAfee to Matles Regarding Supercharger and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, September 30, 1942; 11.
    - Local 901 Outgoing Sam McAfee Correspondence, October 1-November 25, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 92)